decawave.com 2005-02-06

# Untitled Document

Privacy Policy 

The decaWave.com website is an interactive online service operated by decaWave Limited. DecaWave conducts its worldwide business including operations relating to research and development, manufacturing and marketing in Ireland or through wholly-owned subsidiaries incorporated in Ireland, the U.S., the United Kingdom and other countries in which it conducts business. The term "decaWave" is used throughout this website to collectively refer to decaWave Liimited, and its subsidiary companies. decaWave is committed to protecting the privacy of users of this site. This policy explains how decaWave achieves that goal and gives you details of our privacy practices, including a) what information we collect about you when you use this site; b) how the information will be used or disclosed; and c) your rights with respect to our collection and use of your data.

Your Consent

By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

What Information do we collect and why?

We may ask you to provide us with personal information in certain areas of our site on a voluntary basis.

In particular, you may be asked to provide information in the following situations:

Information Requests: If you submit an e-mail requesting information, we will use this information to respond to your request. In order to respond to your request we may make personal information that you submit in these sections available to subsidiaries of decaWave and, in some circumstances to certain of our service providers. These entities may be located primarily within the U.S. and countries within the European Union.  
Contact Services: In many places on the site, you will be provided with contact details for specific individuals. You can contact any named individual by clicking on the e-mail link next to the relevant name. Information that you send to any individual will be used by that person for purposes of responding to your communication. In order to respond to your request, we may make personal information that you submit in these sections available to subsidiaries of decaWave and, in some circumstances, to third party service providers.  
Careers Services: If you want to apply for a position with decaWave through the Careers section of the site, you may be asked to submit general information (such as your name and address), together with a copy of your resume. decaWave will use this information for purposes of processing your hiring application and for corresponding with you. Your application will be kept on file for a minimum of two years. decaWave is an equal opportunities employer. Apart from those policies required by law, decaWave may change its human resources and hiring policies and practices at any time without further notice.  
Passive Information: Currently, we do not use cookies or other technology to gather personal information, although we may do so in the future to enable personalization of information provided on this site. This privacy policy will be updated before we begin to use any such technology.   
How else does decaWave use/disclose Information that it collects from this site?

decaWave may also collect non-personal information, such as IP addresses, numbers of site visits and tracking patterns of page viewing in order to monitor the performance of the site and to make improvements to it.

decaWave will hold all of the personal information that it collects on its computers in Ireland. However, decaWave has subsidiaries in many other jurisdictions, including in the U.S. and Europe, and information may be transferred electronically from time to time between those locations.

In addition, decaWave may from time to time need to disclose your personal information to third parties located in the U.S. or in any other country, but only:

To contractors if necessary to support our business (e.g., technical support providers);  
In connection with the sale, assignment or other transfer of the business of this site; or  
If required to do so by applicable laws, court orders, government regulations or authorities.   
Except as specifically provided above and in this Privacy Policy, decaWave will not disclose personal information to any third party without your prior consent.

Your Rights

Access and Correction: You have a right to know about the personal information that decaWave holds about you. You also have a right to correct, amend or delete the information that decaWave holds about you if it is incorrect. If you wish to exercise these rights please contact us by post or e-mail at the address shown in the "Contact" section below   
External Links

This website provides links to various websites that we do not control. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our website and connected to the website of the organization or company that you selected. Even if an affiliation exists between our website and a third-party website, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and/or data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a website that is linked to our site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

Security

This site incorporates appropriate safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information we have collected and we have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss, misuse and alteration. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide us.

Terms and Modifications to Privacy Policy

decaWave may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, at its discretion and modifications are effective upon being posted on this site. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.

Contact Details

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this site or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this privacy statement you can contact:

Last Updated: December 10, 2001

Click here for Terms of Use Agreement
